satarabia.net 2015-06-08

# Privacy Policy

Satarabia.Com is committed to protecting the privacy of those using our site and the confidentiality of the personal information which our customers provide us with. We use the information we collect to provide services and to ensure that your order is processed smoothly. Beyond that, we only use personal information if volunteered by you. Satarabia.Com will never sell personal information or share personal information with third parties unless these are involved to fulfill your order.

**Satarabia.Com will never sell personal information**

Satarabia.Com will never sell personal information or share personal information with third parties, unless these are involved to fulfill your order. Our employees and associated companies are obliged to respect confidentiality.

**Cookies**

Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. Satarabia.Com uses cookies to recognize you when you return to us. Cookies also enable us to gain information about the use of our services and to enhance our site according to the preferences of our customers. Our cookies contain identifying information. Of course, you can change the settings in your browser and shop at Satarabia.Com without a cookie.  
Should you have further questions regarding our privacy policy, please refer by email Our customer service also helps you if you need information about your data or if you would like to have data corrected. If a change of our privacy policy should become necessary you will always find the actual version on this page.
